Tell me how you think I'm wrong When I say I feel so lost
Tell me why you think your love Can erase all that it cost
Tell me why you look at me Like I'm just a piece of dust
Tell me how you think you know When I give away my trust
Like he's awake and unhappy, it shows In his American flag speedos
Laying back smiling, snacking on flames Flamin' hot cheetos, drownin' old pain
the rest left him behind thought they knew best now he's stuck musing with the soul full of
But he wasn't their victim
Oh, no, not at all
He was their father
Bruises and all
Chat, forgive me
I didn't confess
The truth's a bit messy
Just make it loud
Your daddy's still smiling
Damn, he's proud
Man, what are you doing? I'm sitting here. I'm just in here looking at you a state of shock
What and a state of shock is watching you why did you see your discord?
You're just my discord. Oh
No, I made a discord. I didn't even
remember
Remember when you send me that picture of a habit of a durable
you remember that call right I never I asked you for nude for your nude photos
and he said a picture of South Park let me week's the gerbil from South Park
yeah that wasn't it I wasn't a new right
It wasn't a good it wasn't I know there's a good episode
But it didn't make any sense for what I asked and then you sent me a picture of a giant cartoon gerbil
He asked for nerds and so I just see you there in sir side of my asshole. Oh my god
I'm so happy I was hoping that wasn't the joke
Oh
Welcome to the madness
It's 9 p.m. Lights up Mike's hot chaos in the stream Vita calling in slurring words starting up a scene talking all that trash
Then she flips rage Queen mad at me girl, please the show runs on caffeine size twisted laughing loud whiskey in his veins
Slurrs flying left and right we cut the feed no shame, but the chats on fire can't tame this flame. This ain't your mama
podcast this a runaway train welcome to the madness buckle up tight boot
flashing on cam chat losing their minds Michael getting gong Alex taking flight
it's wild it's wrong and we do it every night
Paige got him simping hearts in the chat but she ain't got time for a dude like
that diamond flirting hard let the girls react it's a freak show party no filter
all fat
Drop the line gone not tonight Alex tried to joke boom sent into the night panel looking sideways
Someone's got a fight producers on mute praying this don't spike diamonds feeling spicy shirts slipping down low
Oops, she says with a wink. That's the whole show sides half asleep. I still cracking jokes slurred out wisdom with a bourbon so glow
No rules just rolls we pretend to play
We're trending in the press
Robin dollars here. What's up? I'm a dog. Yeah, I did like it too guys
I'm not gonna drink the rest of this but I do I'm drinking a bottle of tequila tonight
Me have to go look there's like I just a little bit left
I'm fine. I'm fine guys unless I like
In this time I come with toes in the corner and like screaming for help. Do not call for help
No, don't wait for all my dollars because who's with Gotti?
What makes sense because I knew Romance all was like in the Scientology
God is obviously Scientologist. He tries to like put the Jesuit Jesuit Catholic. Oh, I'm like I'm
Amish fucking Scientologists
Science colleges, you're so obvious
Oh
We're gonna buy these hats where the buddy's like oh
We go to the costume store in Hollywood and buy an Amish hat and think we're Amish people now because people are so dumb
They don't see their body at the costume store in Hollywood
Then let's turn LA and then they're like kind of like they already know but they're like they're too cool to say anything
But I'm not cool so I can tell the whole truth
Fucking Scientologists. Oh, oh, okay, Gotti fair game right fair game Gotti. It was just fair game
It was just a
Suppressive person as peas give me a fucking
Neograft test or MO graph
Whatever
Lighty-tector get all my secrets out and they use my gifts when I quit your fucking stupid church
Okay, it's war on Scientology. Like I basically yeah
I didn't want to like keep it like a secret. It's been this way all along. It's just fucking Scientologists saying they're everything else
Yeah
Let's make sake insane. Let's just drive a person that's like a really cool person. I was a really nice at one point
I was so cool
Let's drive this person insane
And then say oh this person went insane. You can just look him up in a message. They do to everybody else
guys
Don't let me tell you about Scientology
Don't maybe I don't want to tell you about it. It's a nightmare. It's a nightmare
It's an evil maze you'll never get out of do not go to it
They're behind everything they're behind everything guys. This is the last probably video I'll probably make
I'm gonna sit next to the alien because he makes me
Maybe he this is like my best friend right here. This he doesn't judge me. Okay, everyone else judges me
All he does is hold a cat. I wake up in the morning. Oh, here's the cat. That's all I want to see I
Mean, it's all I want anymore. I just want to have a cat presented to me when I wake up
I can cuddle with it for a few minutes
They can't go back to the alien. I'm like, where's Lenore? Where's Lenore?
Well, she has to go back to the aliens for like six hours out of the day
Then Jamie's like, where's Lenore? I'm like, well
Lenore can't come to the
Camera right now because she's in the underworld ruling as the queen, but I mean, I can't say that so I have to say
She's outside meowing. Oh, well, she's dead. Well, I mean Jamie come on, please
Jamie please. No, no Lenore spy. You saw Lenore today. I was not like pretending to like I did not have a Lenore puppet
That is Lenore
She has to go to the underworld for six hours a day. I mean, I can't explain it to you in a simpler way
That is like just the truth. I have to say the truth for like
Like at least 45 seconds
Yeah, and she's also my wife and I mean, it's very complicated. Okay, it gets
Complicated you don't want to go down my the rabbit hole that is
Me, okay, you don't want to go down it. Okay. I'm trying to like
Help you guys. I mean it's like imagine trying to help people and they're like
Pulling you you're like I help people. You're like, oh my my child. I was the best and they're like
They think you're like some kind of like gum under the really what do you think alien? Yeah. Yeah, he knows he knows the truth, too
They think I'm a scum of the earth, right?
And I say they try to really help people you really like
I think one of the last people that loves everybody, they can say, once I'm gone, it's over, like really, once I'm gone, it's over, because I'm so willing to fight a little bit.
I'm like at this point, I'm like, well, I was supposed to die like 15 years ago, I'm still here, so I'm obviously meant to like...
Help the world in some way or else the world would have taken me out like at birth or something like that
I don't know the world knows what to do. The world is smarter than you think
You know the world is just a piece of like dirt. You can just plant things in it. It'll just give you things
You don't have to thank you. You don't have to like appreciate it that you came out of this
This is your mother actually. It's like not sending your mother or mother's day car and one time okay one year I did
Okay, I got stabbed in the ear one year. Okay, someone stabbed me in the ear
I don't want to tell too much of the story, but it was traumatic and then
It was my mom's birthday probably a couple weeks later
And I didn't call them on that day and I I mean I was only that day just like sitting in a corner like saying
What the fuck is going on in my life? And I ain't calling them all of the day
And that was my birthday right nothing, you know everybody else
Right the seven siblings, right?
Everybody else of course
One year on Mother's Day. I called the house. I was in jail
I got arrested one year on Mother's Day. I was like come build me up
My family says let's leave in the fucking jail for the weekend. He's the fucking bastard
They got me Monday morning, right?
They could have bailed me out for Mother's Day dinner.
I could have been bailed out.
Could have happened that Sunday morning
that they bailed me out.
But you know what?
It was meant to be, it was just one of those other lessons
I had to learn.
You know, guys, no matter how drunk I am
or how stupid I sound or whatever,
like I say, I leave myself carrying like many years ago.
But anyway, I'll tell you.
No matter what I think or anything
You
Say you one thing respect your mother. I don't want to be like this
The dad say hey be nice to your mom my dad. I have a good fight to the mom
You know, she's a cancer out of a cat reform where the opposite of the
Zodiac were like the opposite of understanding each other and then she gets offended by everything
I'm always trying to offend right it's like nothing. It's not like a combination
She's the best she is the best mom. I
Hate when people say anything negative about a mother a mother brings Jewish in the world. I get it's like
the mother your mother is like your
Every spirit in the every spirit is a there's like a lot of spirit and like every star is a spirit
like every star is like some kind of like part of the star is like a
human soul that's like going to the
material plane because it wants to live and stuff like that but it's part of the Sun
It's like it's like that it's like the soul is like part of the Sun
It collects all this like debris and dust and finally gives them into like a human being
Which we should look like
Like mud monsters or like some kind of we have at one point and I remember that I remember the mud monster
I remember as a thick person. I remember was a peewee Herman fucking doll
That was the worst lifetime I've ever experienced when I was actually a peewee Herman talking doll
and then I was given some kid on Easter and he was like laughing like pull the string and then as like my voice got
Really high-pitched at some point and I was like
And I would say
I would say uh what's another peewee herman's joke I just like um
Guys you have to put it in the chat. I can't even remember anymore. I am very drunk
But that peewee herman's all that I am that peewee herman's all that I mean it's like
I can't explain it in any other way. Do I make sense? I don't think I do anymore, but it's okay
You know, I say everybody what everybody's like, oh, we want to see somebody crash out
We're gonna see this. What's it was this many crash out? Nobody ever crashed it up
I'm gonna crash out for you because you know what I love you that and I'd love you enough to have a crash at night
What is it? It's uh, everyone put something it's 8 a it's August 8th. It's 88
It's double strength. Remember this is oh psyche crash down that day. Oh my god. Remember that day that psyche
Winner insane
And he was talking to the whole bizarre state, and everyone got really scared.
We sent the police to his house a few times, and like, you know,
even they weren't too scared to come in the door, because they heard this like really loud
frantic yelling at a tablet, and they were like, oh my gosh, we can't handle this.
Okay, because even I'm too much for the police department and the ambulance,
and even you guys, I'm too much for everybody, okay? I understand I'm too much.
myself in the corners and like every I would spread myself so thin so I'm not like affecting you in a
negative way because you know what I'm not here to affect you in a negative way I'm here to like
in a very fatherly energy saying hey you know what you hate me
I think of you as all not like in a pretty Kruger way even though it's very pretty Krugerish
I know it is but it's like you are my children you are my children like it's like
That's how I think of other human beings. It's like they are my children and so anybody
I don't like anybody to be hurt harmed or even like in a negative state because of other people
I don't want anybody
Sad like I'm here
Basically make people happy and if I don't make you happy, and I'm really sorry. I know I've been really
Okay, like how much of the bottles gone is like that even the heart guys
This is just it's just being started, but please don't tell anybody about this live
This is very simple to play 66 people are here. No, please everyone leave everyone leave
I don't want anybody here. Hold on. I can't even see I can't read the chat anymore because it's too
Like everything's gone blurry right now
I think it's the end guy. It has to be the end. I wouldn't do this
I wouldn't do this if it wasn't like the right thing. Yeah, but don't worry. Don't worry. It's fine
Alien will be here. Thank you. Look. That's my replacement. He will look look here. He's cuter than me
Look, he's smile. He smiles you guys you see the smile. He's smiling guys
He is funnier than me this alien like he I wake up every morning. I look at the alien
He's like you have a cat
I'm like, I'd love you. You're my best friend
Oliver why I wasn't alien to give me a cat every morning like he's here
Slung with the cat honestly guys every morning guys
This is why I'm like not ever really really that sad because every morning
Wake up and tricks is kind of the blanket and then he's like comes up as close as you can to me
And then he starts like purring really loud and look we just sit there with a purring for like two hours
I was there and I'll be like I think I like that I went to heaven because I
They don't should be as lucky to be like so happy and blessed. It's not the cat purring nice to you in the morning
Yeah, I don't know really this is the drill. I'm sorry
It's like
I'd say a rubber band, it's like the rubber band is pulled so far, and then it's like
mentioned the rubber band is that it breaks or the rubber band like like puts
black back to the proposal and like
It's like puts itself out in the world. That's what I do and uh, so I'm sorry if I did something wrong tonight, but
I'll be clipped in like it. I'm not gonna be like everyone's gonna laugh and the Tommy Jays is like you're stupid
and everywhere I band is that I'm such a fucking bad person and asshole and
I'm like worthless and nothing and no one and why are you thinking about even existing on the world?
No, don't guys don't anything ever tell you that you're not worthy of anything. It's like, you know, you're human being you're here
you have the spirit of God and the spirit of God is in everybody.
I really do believe that here, from the bottom of my heart, I believe the spirit of God is in everybody
and we're all part of God. And it's like, it's just expecting anybody or hurting anybody's feelings
or like trying to think...
Take any part of their
self-confidence or love of themselves away is like akin to like a murder and
Trying to hurt people and wanting to send people to hell. I'm bringing all these negative things into it
So all I have to say is like, you know guys it's like
All you can do is love everybody and not hurt anybody never hurt any person. They have no ill will towards people just
Go in the loving spirit
and in the spirit of non harm to anything I mean I feel bad if I step on a
caterpillar or you know a bug or something that I feel bad it might be
like maybe they'll be able to reincarnate into a better life because of that but
I don't that's not but I'm concerned about all I'm concerned about I don't want to
harm any anything or anybody and
That's all I'm about is like not a harm living in the world and they like almost like almost like I'm not even here
I don't I'll live my little like I want to live in my little like 100 square feet and
Whatever I want to do in 100 square feet I can do but anything outside of the square feet
I want to like tread very lightly and not hurt anybody and just love people
But guys the more I'm honest that I'm just gonna clip then I say oh this person's insane
And it's like this is like he's a bad person and there's nothing about it. It's really considered bad or like
People are gonna say it's not a bad person. So just be ready for it. But people that suck by me. I appreciate you
I'm gonna not kind of like keep you on and like listen to my bullshit right now
So, I, but I want you to know, guys, that my what happens, I love you, okay?
I love you, and I would never let any harm come on you.
If any way possible, I could prevent any harm from you.
I would take it on myself for any of you.
I really would.
For any of you, I would take any harm that is ever to come to you onto myself.
And I say that
As a statement and I hope the food and I pray that comes true
I want anything that bad to happen. I want anything bad to happen to me rather than you
I read anything bad happened to me
So that's that's all I ask for tonight is like anything negative in your life
But you see the positive and may I just be all the negatives, but I love you guys
Thank you guys
People thank you guys for just being here. I know like so many people are here and like great friends and like
I know a lot of you guys love me and stuff
I want to thank you guys because it's like really as the
Super now as like, you know, I had the best time of my life doing this show at the best time of my life
And it's like that's why it's like
Everything beyond this point is a dream. It's like, oh, that's like
Kids these will happen right good exactly happening the whole time. They have the it's like the whole time the whole show
It's all been happy
Happy things Robin like taking the negative away from me. It really has
But I don't want to be stupid, but I love you guys and I just want to thank you for being part of my life, okay?
I know I'm really really dumb, but okay the other wants to say good night to you, okay?
Thank you guys for being here. I love you. I love you. I love you. Don't forget. I love you, okay?